themortonreport.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy | TMR

TMR ("TMR") knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting or using the TMR website and domain name, and any other linked pages, features, content, or any of our services offered from time to time by TMR in connection therewith (collectively, the "Website"), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?  
This Privacy Policy covers TMR' treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that TMR gathers when you are accessing TMR' Website and when you use TMR services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that TMR does not own or control, or to individuals that TMR does not employ or manage.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES TMR COLLECT?  
The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services and to allow our users to set up a user account and profile that can be used to interact with other users through the Website. In connection with the Website, we request and display some personal information to other users and visitors of Website, which allows users to identify each other. We collect the following types of information from our customers.

**Personal Information You Provide to Us:**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include your name, user name, email address, IP address, and browser information. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as allowing you to interact with other users, improving the content of the Website, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new features.

**Personal Information Collected Automatically:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website or services. TMR automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested.

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. TMR only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Website or services so that we can make the Website appealing to as many customers as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our site. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and our Website, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. Again, TMR never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

**Email Communications:**  
We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from TMR if your computer supports this type of program. TMR uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful and improve our service. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please unsubscribe from the communication using the link provided in the footer of the email, this will blacklist you from further communications from us, with the exception of any administrative related notices.

**Mailing Lists:**  
TMR offers a free subscription to the TMR website. When you sign up to the TMR website, you may receive from time to time a newsletter as well as notifications of replies to comments you make on the website. Additional TMR mailing lists will be available for you as well. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from any website, users must submit information including a valid email address. 

Users who choose to sign up for this site will receive periodic newsletters, and separately, if users sign up for the new post notifications, they will also receive notifications when new posts are made on the site. These services are independent of each other, and a user can exist in either service, or both. If you do not wish to receive emails from TMR, you can unsubscribe at any time.

**What About Cookies?**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. TMR cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Website's most attractive features.

Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by TMR and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

WILL TMR SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?  
Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below.

**Agents:**  
We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, TMR' agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

**User profiles:**  
User profile information including users' name, email address, and other information you enter may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Website. Email addresses are used to add new User Submissions (as defined in our [Terms of Use](http://www.themortonreport.com/terms-of-use/)) to user profiles and to communicate through User Submissions. Users' email addresses will not be directly revealed to other users by Company, except, when the user is "connected" to another user via a shared group membership, or an invitation, or if the user has chosen to include their email address in their User Profile.

**Communication in response to User Submissions:**  
As part of the Website and Services, you will receive from Company email and other communication relating to your User Submissions. You acknowledge and agree that by posting such User Submissions, Company may send you email and other communication that it determines in its sole discretion relate to your User Submissions.

**Business Transfers:**  
In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if TMR, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that TMR goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of TMR may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

**Protection of TMR and Others:**  
We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of TMR, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**With Your Consent:**  
Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?  
Your TMR account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

TMR endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, TMR cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

The Website may contain links to other sites. TMR is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Website.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?  
TMR allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list will change as our Website changes.

  * Name and password
  * Email address
  * User profile information 

WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?  
As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information to use, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain TMR features.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the "What Personal Information Can I Access" section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

You may request deletion of your TMR account by sending an email to [webmaster@themortonreport.com](mailto:webmaster@themortonreport.com). Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate this by changing your account settings. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the TMR Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
TMR may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at TMR site, please send us a detailed message to: [webmaster@themortonreport.com](mailto:webmaster@themortonreport.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: April 24, 2011
